When we first defined our tables we defined
当我们第一次定义表格，我们使用
the relationships in terms of constraints. Now, we
限制来定义表格直接的关系。 现在，我们
are going to implement that relationship into our
将要去把这些表格的关系应用到
query using a join this join will allow us
我们的查询中，在此，使用join 就会使我们
to query the weather table for values from
可以通过一些特殊的地址
a specific location setting. We'll start by adding a
来查询天气的表格。我们需要将SQL Ite 查询的
SQL Ite query builder class variable at the
创建者类加入在
top of weather provider. We'll initialize the SQLI to
天气创建者之前。 我们也需要初始化 SQLI
query builder in the static constructor for the
查询的创建者， 使用一个静态的类
class, describing the join between both tables. Note,
并且要描述在两个表格中这个join。 注意，
since both tables have a column named _ID.
既然两个表格有一个共同的列叫做_ID.
We must explicitly use the table name in
我们必须要明确的使用这个表格的名称，
order to disambiguate which underscore ID we are
这样才能消除在join里使用下划线ID时
talking about in the join. Then we can
产生的歧义。然后我们就可以来
define the query. The query is to find
定义查询啦。 这个查询有一个
using the question mark replacement syntax. These question marks
使用问号替代的语法。这些问号
will be replaced by the query parameters. Since we
将会被查询的参数代替。 既然我们
allow people to specify the start date in the URI,
允许大家在URI中使用特指的开始时间
we're also going to add a second selection, which includes
我们也需要增加第二个选项， 这个第二选项包括
checking to see whether date text is greater than or
去检查日期的值是否大于或等比
equal to our parameter. Next, we'll add a method to
我们放入的参数。 下面，我们将加入两个方法去
get the weather by location entry, using the same query
通过具体地理位置来获取天气， 同意，我们使用的时相同的获取
builder. Note, that we fetch the parameters from our URI.
创建者。注意，这就是我们从URI获取到参数，
And though the string arrays, they can be substituted into
经管这些事字符串数组，他们依然可以被在查询中取代
our query. Note that if URI does not contain a start date we actually use
注意，乳沟在URI中不存在开始日期的情况我们实际上使用了
a different selection. Finally, we add the function
另一种不同的选项。 最后，我们在查询中加入我们
into the query routine of our content provider.
内容提供的函数方法。